// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question:"A car travels a distance of 240 miles at a speed of 60 miles per hour. How long does it take to complete the journey?",
  answer: "2 hrs",
  options: [
    "1 hrs",
    "2 hrs",
    "5 hrs",
    "9 hrs"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "A train covers a distance of 400 kilometers at an average speed of 100 km/h. How long does it take to complete the journey?",
  answer: "4 hrs",
  options: [
    "1 hrs",
    "4 hrs",
    "5 hrs",
    "9 hrs"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "If a cyclist travels at a speed of 20 km/h, how long will it take to cover a distance of 80 kilometers?",
  answer: "4 hrs",
  options: [
    "1 hrs",
    "9 hrs",
    "5 hrs",
    "4 hrs"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "A bus covers a distance of 360 miles at an average speed of 40 miles per hour. How long does it take to complete the journey?",
  answer: "9 hrs",
  options: [
    "11 hrs",
    "9 hrs",
    "10 hrs",
    "4 hrs"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "A plane travels at a speed of 800 kilometers per hour. How long will it take to travel a distance of 4000 kilometers?",
  answer: "4.5 hrs",
  options: [
    "1.5 hrs",
    "2.5 hrs",
    "3.5 hrs",
    "4.5 hrs"
  ]
},


   {
 numb: 6,
 question: "If a car travels at a speed of 70 miles per hour, how long will it take to travel a distance of 350 miles?",
  answer: "5 hrs",
  options: [
    "3 hrs",
    "9 hrs",
    "10 hrs",
    "4 hrs"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 7,
  question: "A person walks at a speed of 5 km/h. How long will it take to walk a distance of 15 kilometers?",
   answer: "3.5 hrs",
   options: [
    "1 hrs",
    "2.5 hrs",
    "3.5 hrs",
    "4 hrs"
  ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A train covers a distance of 480 miles at an average speed of 80 miles per hour. How long does it take to complete the journey?",
     answer:"10 hrs",
     options: [
      "3 hrs",
      "9 hrs",
      "10 hrs",
      "4 hrs"
    ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "If a cyclist travels at a speed of 15 km/h, how long will it take to cover a distance of 45 kilometers?",
       answer: "4 hrs",
       options: [
        "3 hrs",
        "9 hrs",
        "10 hrs",
        "4 hrs"
      ]
      },
      {
        numb: 10,
        question: "A car travels a distance of 300 kilometers at a speed of 60 km/h. How long does it take to complete the journey?",
        answer: "4.5 hrs",
        options: [
          "11 hrs",
          "9 hrs",
          "10 hrs",
          "4.5 hrs"
        ]
        }
];